

CONTACT ME

vebarina@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/veronicabarina



github.com/vebarina



+372 5603 8208

ADDRESS



Tallinn, Estonia

SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3 (including bootstrap, tailwind, SCSS, Sass)

JavaScript ES6 (including TypeScript, Vue.js, Vuex, React.js, React Native, Next.js)

Unit, integration and component testing (Jest, React Testing Library, Vue Test Utils, Cypress)

Git

MySQL

VERONICA BARINA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated, proactive, and goal-oriented software developer with a drive for continuous learning and self-improvement.

I am experienced in working in small to medium Agile teams with a focus on Scrum methodologies.

I have great communication skills and attention to detail, and I excel in collaborative team environments as well as when working autonomously.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Codatina | Remote | October 2023 - Present

• I help digital agencies who need extra development resources in their projects, using technologies such as React.js, React Native, Vue.js, among others.

Software Developer

Konfuzio | Remote | April 2022 - October 2023

• As a part of the Frontend team, I am responsible for implementing new features using Vue.js, Vuex, Buefy, Git (and GitHub/GitLab), Vue Test Utils, and Cypress, delivering a high-quality product, as well as improving existing features and codebase, fixing bugs, supporting clients, and updating our documentation. My work can be found in the following open-source repository.

Freelance React Native Developer

Pipet App | Remote | Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

• I was responsible for helping develop the frontend of a pet mobile app with React Native.

LANGUAGES

Spanish → Native speaker

English → Bilingual

French —— Conversational

Estonian —— Beginner

Freelance React Developer

Bien Consulting | Remote | May 2021 - Nov 2021

• I was responsible for creating the React.js frontend for a cross-platform sleep tracking app project.

EDUCATION

Mastering React

Code With Mosh | Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

Beginner JavaScript

Wes Bos | Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

CSS Grid

Wes Bos | Jun 2021

Java from Scratch

Software Development Academy (SDA) | Nov 2020 - Jul 2021

Introduction to CSS3

University of Michigan - Coursera | May 2020

Introduction to HTML5

University of Michigan - Coursera | Apr 2020 - May 2020